Bennet, Augustus W.; Papers apap225
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Augustus Bennet Papers
1935-1948
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Bennet, Augustus W., 1897-1983
apap225
16.13 cubic ft.
The collection contains materials from Augustus Bennet's campaigns for the House of Representatives and files from his subsequent service in Congress.
Biographical History
Augustus Witschief Bennet was born in New York City on October 7, 1897, the son of William Stiles Bennet, who served in the U.S. Congress from 1905-1911. Augustus Bennet attended the public schools of New York City and Washington, D.C., and graduated from Amherst College in 1918. During World War I, he served in the United States Naval Reserve Flying Corps with the rating of chief quartermaster from June 8, 1918, to January 19, 1919. He graduated from Columbia University Law School in 1921, was admitted to the bar the same year, and commenced practice in Newburgh, N.Y.
Bennet was a United States referee in bankruptcy from 1923-1944. He initially attempted a campaign for Congress in 1942 and was subsequently elected in 1944 to the 79th Congress from the 29th Congressional District of New York. Bennet defeated Hamilton Fish, an incumbent who had served 24 years in Congress. Fish initially defeated Bennet in the Republican primary, but Bennet then ran in the general election on the Democratic, American Labor, Liberal and Good Government tickets. Bennet subsequently sat in Congress as a Republican. Bennet served from January 3, 1945-January 3, 1947, but was not re-elected in 1946. He then resumed the practice of law.
Bennet married Maxine Layne in 1929 and had three children. He later resided in Laguna Hills, Calif. until his death in Concord, Mass. on June 5, 1983. His ashes are interred at Cedar Hills Mausoleum in Newburgh.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of materials from Augustus Bennet's Congressional election campaigns, correspondence, bills, invitations, subject files, news releases, and speeches. There also are 16 scrapbooks, composed predominantly of newspaper clippings and memorabilia, documenting Bennet's campaigns and subsequent Congressional service.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is arranged alphabetically. There are no series.
Acquisition Information
In 1963 Augustus Bennet initially donated his papers to Syracuse University. The papers were transferred to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in 2006.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted with the exception of one file related to service academy appointments.
Politics and Politicians; Bennet, Augustus, W., 1897-1983; New York (State)--Politics and government; Political Campaigns—New York (State); Correspondence; Files by subject; Bills (legislative records); Clippings (information artifacts).
- 2nd Ad, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
- A- Several, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Adams, Mr. Gridley, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Addresses Washington, 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Advertisement, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Advertisement of Other Candidates, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Advertising Set Up, 1944; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Aero- Administrations (1 of 2), 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Aero- Administrations (2 of 2), 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Agriculture, 1943; 1945-1946; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Agriculture, 1944; 1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Agriculture- Sev, 1940; 1946; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Agriculture Yearbook, 1945; 1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- AIP Endorsement, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Airport Program E.M. Van Name, 1945; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Alaska, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Alfred Envelope Co., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- American Creed- Delaware County, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- American Creed- Delaware County High Schools, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- American Creed- Orange County High Schools, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- American Creed- Rockland County High Schools, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Amherst College, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Andrews, Hon. William T., Member of State Assembly, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Angell, M. B., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Annapolis General - RESTRICTED, 1942-1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Must consult an archivist before viewing this material.
- Anonymous, 1945; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Applications, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Arax Photo Studios, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Autobiography- A.W. Bennet, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Autographs, 1945; 1946 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- A.W. Bennet Radio Speech, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- B- General (1 of 3), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
- B- General (2 of 3), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
- B- General (3 of 3), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- B and L General, 1946 March (Box 2, Folder 2)
- B and L General, 1946 April (Box 2, Folder 3)
- B and L General, 1946 June (Box 2, Folder 4)
- B and L General, 1946 July (Box 2, Folder 5)
- B and L General, 1946 September (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Ballot (Set Up), Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Beacon Light and Fisher, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Beacon News, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Bennet and Bennet, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Bennet, A.W., Personal (1 of 2), 1945; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bennet, A.W., Personal (2 of 2), 1945; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Bennet Bills, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bennet Broadcast, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Bennet for Congress Committees (Sponsorship), 1944 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Bennet Letter for Delaware County, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Bennet Radio Speech, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Bennet Statement on Election Results and on Primary Results, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Bennet, Wm., Personal II (1 of 2), 1946; Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Bennet, Wm., Personal II (2 of 2), 1946; Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Bennet, Wm. S., 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Bennet's Pictures, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Bernard, Mrs. Marian, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Berry, Jas. S., 1945; Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Bids (1 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Bids (2 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Bills- General, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Bills Payable, 1940; 1942 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Bird, Clarence E., 1944; Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
- "Black Mail", 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Boice, Mr. Russell, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Brandt, Mrs. Evelyn, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Breakdown of 1940 Democratic Votes (Congressional) in Rockland County, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Brewster Standard, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Briker, Mr. Harry, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Brown, Mr. Alfred and Mrs. Phyllis, 1944; Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Budget, 1942; Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Budget, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Budget, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Budget for Election, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Buttons and Lapel Tags, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- C Directory, 1945; 1946 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- C- General (1 of 2), 1945; 1946; Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
- C- General (2 of 2), 1945; 1946; Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Calendars, 1945; Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Campaign 1942, 1942 May (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Campaign 1942, 1942 June (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Campaign 1942, 1942 July (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Campaign 1942 (1 of 2), 1942 August -September (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Campaign 1942 (2 of 2), 1942 August -September (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Campaign 1942, 1940; 1942 October-December (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Campaign 1946, 1946 May-June (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Campaign 1946, 1946 June (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Campaign 1946, 1946 July-August (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Campaign Material, 1945; Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Campaign Organization, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Campaign Radio Talks, 1942; Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Cartels, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Change of Address Letters, 1944; Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Chester News, Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
- China, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- C.I.O. Political Action Committee, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Coal, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Coast Guard, 1945; Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Commandy- Roth Co., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Committee to Defeat Hamilton Fish, 1944; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Congress Committee, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Contracts, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Contributors to Campaign Fund (Form Letter to), 1944; Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Controversial Letters, Speech, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Cooperatives (1 of 2), 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Cooperatives (2 of 2), 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Copy for Monday Ad, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Copy for Friday Ad, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Cornwall Local, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1944; Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Correspondents, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Coulter, Mr. D.W., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Crews, Mr. Floyd H., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Crist, Mr. Charles, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Cullen, Mr. Thomas, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Delaware County, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Democratic Committee of the Town of Monroe, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Dexter, Mrs. L.D., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Dick Malkin: Material on Hamilton Fish, 1944; Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Dinner- Hally (at Palatine 10/16/44), 1944 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Directions to Supporters and Workers, Undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
- District Results, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Donahue, Mr., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Election Estimate, Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Election Material, 1942-1943; Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Election Material, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- E.R.H., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Express Receipts, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- External Campaign News Release II, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Extra Copies News Release, 1945; Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Facts about Fish, 1941-1942; 1946; Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Famers Bulletins I (1 of 2), 1945 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Famers Bulletins I (2 of 2), 1945 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Farmers Bulletins II (1 of 2), 1945 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Farmers Bulletins II (2 of 2), 1945 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Farmers Bulletins III (1 of 2), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Farmers Bulletins III (2 of 2), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Farmer's Union- Sullivan City, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Farr, Miss Isabelle, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- First Ad, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Fish Cartoon (Letters to Various Organizations Pictured), 1944 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Fish Material, 1942; Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Fish- Remarks- etc., Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Fish- Voting Record, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Finances, 1942; Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Flag Day Address, 1942; Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Foreman, James F., Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Franco, Persio Celeste, Undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Friends of Democracy, Inc., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- G- General (1 of 2), 1944-1946; Undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
- G- General (2 of 2), 1944-1946; Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
- General B and L, 1946 May (Box 5, Folder 1)
- General Correspondence, 1944; Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- General Legislation B and L, 1945; Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- General Legislation Testimonies (1 of 3), 1946; Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- General Legislation Testimonies (2 of 3), 1946; Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- General Legislation Testimonies (3 of 3), 1946; Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- General Outdoor Advertising, 1944; Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Gettysburg Address, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Goldshine, Mr. Murray, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Goldsmith, Arthur, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Goldstein, Benjamin M., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Goldstein, Benjamin M., 1945; Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
- The Goshen Democrat, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Gov. Dewey's Picture (MAT), Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Granger, Mr. Lester B., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Grant, Milton J., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Greystone Studios Inc., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Guylay, L.R., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- H- General (1 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
- H- General (2 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Hale, Robert, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Halleck, Chas. A., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Harlem Valley Times Amenia, 1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Hamilton Fish Vote, 1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Harriman, Mr. E. R., 1942 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Harwick Valley, 1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Hawaii, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Hayes, Helen, Speech, 1944; Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Hayes, Mrs., Pictures, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Hearings, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Highway Alert, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Hill and Fish Testimony, 1942-1943; Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Hobbs Bill, 1945; Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Hollenbeck, Mrs. Ruth, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Home Owners Loan Corporation, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Hornbeck, Mr. Van, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Hospitals, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Hospitals- Veterans, 1944-1945 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Housing, Federal (1 of 2), 1946; Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Housing, Federal (2 of 2), 1946; Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Hudson Valley Sunday Career Poughkeepsie, Undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
- I- General, 1945; Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Immediate Release, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Immigration (1 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Immigration (2 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Immigration, 1946 January; Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Immigration, 1946 February (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Immigration, 1946 March (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Immigration, 1946 April (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Immigration, 1946 May (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Immigration, 1946 June (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Immigration, 1946 July (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Income Tax, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Income Tax Returns, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Independent Committee, Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Independent Republican, Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Infant Care, 1946; Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Insurance, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Insurance B and L, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- International Petition, 1944-1945; Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Interstate Commerce Commission, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Invitations, 1945 January; Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Invitations, 1945 February (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Invitations, 1945 March (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Invitations, 1945 April (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Invitations, 1945 May (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Invitations, 1945 June (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Invitations, 1945 July (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Invitations, 1945 August; Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Invitations, 1945 September (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Invitations, 1945 October (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Invitations, 1945 November (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Invitations, 1945 December (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Italy, 1946; Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
- J-General, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Jewish Affairs (1 of 2), 1945; 1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Jewish Affairs (1 of 2), 1945; 1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Joe's Material, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- K- General, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Kenneth and Clark, 1945; 1946 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Kyle, A.C. Dr. Gen., 1945; 1946 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- L- General, 1945; Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Labor, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Labor B and L, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Labor B and L II (1 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Labor B and L II (2 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Labor B and L III (1 of 2), 1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Labor B and L III (2 of 2), 1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Lend- Lease, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Letter No. 3 "Joe", 1942 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Letters, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Letters- Dick Scandrett, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Letters Dictated By Mr. Bennet, 1944; Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Letters, Dutchess Co. Committee, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Letters of Support, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Library of Congress, 1939; 1941; 1943; 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- List of Newspapers, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Lists, 1945; Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Loeb, Mr. James, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- M- General (1 of 2), 1945; Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
- M- General (2 of 2), 1945; Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Mahapac Mercury, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Manpower Seal, 1945; Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Material and Book Matches, 1944; Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- McGiffert, Mr. Wm. J., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Medicine Legislation, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Merchant Marine Institute, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Middletown, 1942; Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Middletown Star Eagle, 1942; Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Miguel, Major M.C., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Millbrook Round Table, Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Miller, Mr. Wm. L., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous General, 1944; January 1945; Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous General, 1943-1944; February 1946; Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous General, 1945 March (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous General, 1945 April (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous General, 1945 May (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous General, 1945 June (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous General, 1945 July (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous General, 1945 August (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Miscellaneous General, 1945 September (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous General, 1945 October (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous General, 1945 November (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous General, 1945 December (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous General, 1946 January (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous General, 1946 February (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous General, 1946 March (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous General, 1946 April (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous General, 1946 May (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous General, 1946 June (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous General, 1946 July; Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous General, 1946 August (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous General, 1946 September (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous General, 1946 October (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Newsclippings, 1942; Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Montgomery Standard Reporter, 1942; Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Morris, Newbold, Letter, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- N- General, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Negroes, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
- New York Daily News, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
- New York Times, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Newburgh, Albert P. Fyrmier, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Newburgh Democratic City Committee, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Newburgh News, 1942; Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Newburgh Office (1 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Newburgh Office (2 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- News of the Highland, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
- News Releases, 1945; Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
- News Releases (1 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
- News Releases (2 of 2), 1945-1946; Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
- News Releases, 1946; Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Newspapers, 1944-1945; Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Newspapers, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Nurses' Draft Bill, 1945; Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Nyack, New York (1 of 2), 1944; Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Nyack, New York (2 of 2), 1944; Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
- O- General, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
- O.D.T.- General, 1944-1945; Undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
- O.P.A., 1945 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- O.P.A., 1945-1946 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- O.P.A., 1946 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- O.P.A., 1946; Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
- O.P.A. B and L, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- O.P.A. B and L II (1 of 3), 1946 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- O.P.A. B and L II (2 of 3), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- O.P.A. B and L II (3 of 3), 1946 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- O.P.A. B and L III, 1946; Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
- O.P.A. B and L IV (1 of 2), 1946; Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
- O.P.A. B and L IV (2 of 2), 1946; Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
- O.P.A. B and L V, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
- O.P.A. B and L VI, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- O.P.A. General I (1 of 2), 1945; Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
- O.P.A. General I (2 of 2), 1945; Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
- O.P.A. News II (1 of 2), 1945 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- O.P.A. News II (2 of 2), 1945 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- O.W.L., 1944-1946 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Oil and Gas, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- O'Neill, Mr. Edward G., 1944; Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
- O'Neill, Mr. Wm., 1944 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Orange County Courier, 1942; Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Orange County Letter Committee, Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Orange County Lists, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Orange County Post, 1942; Undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Orange County Yes Cards, Undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Ostegren, Mr. Edwin, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Overseas Services Men, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Pawling News Chronicle, Undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Pending Letters to Editors, 1944; Undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Petition Material, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Petition Material- Liberal Party, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Petition Names, 1944; Undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Petition Tax, 1944; Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Petitions Regarding Use of Grain for Beverages, 1945; Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Pine Bush News, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Placard with Blowup of Newspaper Clipping about Plans to Defeat Hamilton Fish, 1942 August (Oversized 8)
- Porter, Mr. Tom, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Post Cards Mailed (Completed Circulation), Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Poughkeepsie Eagle News, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Poughkeepsie New Yorker, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Press News Releases (1 of 2), 1942; 1944; Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Press News Releases (2 of 2), 1942; 1944; Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Press- Newspaper Letters Subscribing to, 1944; Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Press Release, 1942; Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Primary Campaign, 1942; Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Primary Material, 1944; Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Primary Paid Bills, 1944; Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Prince, Leslie (Address by), 1944 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Putnam County's Republican, 1942; Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Rabbi Bloom Telegram to Dewey, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Radio Address (WJZ- New York) (Mr. Bennet), Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Radio Addresses, Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Radio Addresses (Helen Hayes), Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Radio Addresses (Monticello), 1944; Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Radio Addressed (Spot Announcements), Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Radio Contracts, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Radio Debate (Notes on Fish - Bennet Debate), Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Radio Station in New York City - Correspondence, 1944; Undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Rally Material, 1944; Undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Ratcliff, Mr. J.D, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Red Hook Advertiser, Undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Registration, Undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Report From Worker- Ceddes, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Republican City Committee (Finance Committee), Undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Republican National Committee, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- RE: Absentee Ballots, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- RE: Bennet- Hayes Tour of Delaware County, 1944; Undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
- RE: Cronin Petition, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- RE: School Debate- Bennet vs. Fish (Delhi School), 1944 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- The Rhinebeck Gazette, Undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Rockland County List, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Rogers, Fred S., Telegrams, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- San Francisco Conf., 1945; Undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Savell, Mrs. Isabelle, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Savell, Mrs. Morton K., 1945 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Schimmel, Mr. Sidney, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Scrapbook One, 1942 May-August (Oversized 1)
- Scrapbook Two, 1942 May-October (Oversized 2)
- Scrapbook Three, 1944 April-October (Oversized 3)
- Scrapbook Four, 1944 June-1945 January (Oversized 4)
- Scrapbook Five, 1944 July (Oversized 5)
- Scrapbook Six, 1944 July-August (Oversized 4)
- Scrapbook Seven, 1944 August-October (Oversized 6)